Missing hover:text-black: page.tsx -> tracking-widest bg-terminal-green text-black hover:bg-terminal-green-dark border-none px-6
Missing hover:text-black: page.tsx -> w-full mt-4 bg-terminal-green text-black hover:bg-terminal-green border-none flex items-center justify-center gap-2
Missing hover:text-black: page.tsx -> tracking-widest bg-terminal-green text-black hover:bg-terminal-green-dark border-none px-6
Missing hover:text-black: page.tsx -> bg-terminal-green text-black border-terminal-green hover:bg-terminal-green/80 gap-2 text-xs font-black shadow-[0_0_15px_rgba(0,255,136,0.3)]
Missing hover:text-black on cyan: page.tsx -> w-full bg-terminal-cyan text-black hover:bg-terminal-cyan/80 font-black tracking-widest uppercase py-6 rounded-none mt-4 shadow-[0_4px_0_0_#008888]
Missing hover:text-black: page.tsx -> w-full bg-terminal-green text-black hover:bg-terminal-green/80 font-black tracking-widest uppercase py-6 rounded-none mt-4 shadow-[0_4px_0_0_#008844]
Missing hover:text-black on cyan: page.tsx -> w-full bg-terminal-cyan text-black hover:bg-terminal-cyan font-bold tracking-widest uppercase gap-2
